Guide to the Sozialistisches Buro Records, 1969-1987
Department of Special Collections
Sozialistisches Buro Records,
1969-1987
Special Collections M0913
10.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 1997
Biography
West German protest group which published the left wing journal "Links - Sozialistische Zeitung" as well as numerous pamphlets, handouts, and propaganda leaflets.
Scope and Content
Organizational records, including minutes, memos, files, etc., arranged by date.
Access terms
Socialistische Buero. Rundbrief; Socialism--Germany--1945-1990; Germany--History--1945-1990; Ausserparlamentarische Opposition
Container List
- Beginning 1969- 1970, Aug 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1970, Sept 9 - 1971, Dec 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1972, Jan 1 - 1973, March 31 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1973, April 1 - 1974, April 30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1974, May 1 - 1975, Jan 31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 1975, Jan 2 - 1975, Aug 15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1975, Aug 16 - 1976, March 31 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 1976, April 1 - 1976, Sept 24 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 1976, Sept 25 - 1976, Dec 14 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 1976, Dec 15 - 1977, May 9 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 1977, Oct 5 - 1977, Aug 31 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 1977, Sept. 1 - 1977, Nov 30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 1977, Dec 1 - 1978, March 15 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 1978, March 16 - 1978, July 15 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- 1978, July 16 - 1978, Sept 30 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 1978, Oct 1 - 1979, Apr 20 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- 1979, Apr 21 - 1979, Dec 31 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- 1980, Jan 1 - 1981, May 31 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- 1981, June 1 - 1985, April 30 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- SB-Rundbrief Ausgaben 1-17 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- SB-Rundbrief Ausgaben 18-54 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- SB-Rundbrief Ausgaben 55-90 (Box 7, Folder 22)